RENATA TUKIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer



renata.tukic@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/renata-tukic

ABOUT ME

I've been learning the basics of JavaScript for a while now. I enjoy researching, thinking about a problem, and finding creative solutions for website design and functionality. I would appreciate the opportunity to work as a Front-end Web Developer.

IT SKILLS

HTML 5

CSS 3

JavaScript

Responsive design

Sass

Bootstrap

React

Firebase & NoSQL

Git

PROJECTS

<u>Portfolio</u> – my portfolio contains a description and a link to my projects

https:github.com/renkodiranje

ENVIRONMENT

I work in a Windows environment.

LANGUAGES

English languge - intermediate level

PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

I am a diligent, responsible, creative.

EDUCATION

IT Bootcamp

11/2022-02/2023

Web development (JS + React)

Krojaceva skola

03/2023

Step to work - internship for front end

Faculty of Medicine, University of Nis 2008/2017

Msc Pharmacy

Medical school "Dr Milenko Hadzic", Nis

2004/2008

Pharmaceutical technician

WORK EXPERIENCE

07/2020-07/2021

"Vik Invest DOO" - cashier

- carrying out cash, credit, or check transactions with customers
- responsibility for the cash register 11/2017-06/2018

"Goodwill" pharmacy - apprentice pharmacist

Learning about a process of:

- verifying prescriptions and dispensing medications
- ordering, storing, and distributing drugs and medical equipment
- advising patients on self-medication

HOBBY

I used to dance Tango Argentino during my studies.